(this.webpackJsonppopculturequiz=this.webpackJsonppopculturequiz||[]).push([[0],[,,,,,function(e,a,i){},,,function(e,a,i){e.exports=i(15)},,,,,function(e,a,i){},function(e,a,i){},function(e,a,i){"use strict";i.r(a);var n=i(0),t=i.n(n),o=i(7),s=i.n(o),r=(i(13),i(14),i(1)),u=i(2),h=i(4),l=i(3),d=(i(5),[{question:"What is alterego of Batman",options:["Clark kent","Bruce Wayne","Diana prince","Thomas wayne"],answer:"Bruce Wayne",id:121},{question:"What is Earth Name of Superman",options:["Clark kent","Bruce Wayne","Diana prince","Thomas wayne"],answer:"Clark kent",id:122},{question:"Who has the invisible jet?",options:["Clark kent","Bruce Wayne","Diana prince","Thomas wayne"],answer:"Diana prince",id:123},{question:"Who is speedster died during crisis on infinite earths",options:["Bart Allen","Wally West","Barry Allen","Jay Garrick"],answer:"Barry Allen",id:124},{question:"What is alterego of Aquaman",options:["Clark kent","Bruce Wayne","Diana prince","Arthur Curry"],answer:"Arthur Curry",id:125},{question:"Who is father of Batman",options:["Clark kent","Bruce Wayne","Thomas wayne","Arthur Curry"],answer:"Thomas wayne",id:126},{question:"Which Robin becomes Nightwing",options:["Dick grayson","Jason todd","Tim drake","Conner kent"],answer:"Dick grayson",id:127},{question:"What is alterego of Cyborg",options:["Victor Stone","Jason todd","Tim drake","Conner kent"],answer:"Victor Stone",id:128},{question:"What is earth name of supergirl",options:["Kara Danvers","Carol danvers","Alex danvers","Barbara gordon"],answer:"Kara Danvers",id:129},{question:"Who is youngest robin",options:["Dick grayson","Jason todd","Tim drake","Damian wayne"],answer:"Damian wayne",id:130}]),c=[{question:"What is alterego of Superboy",options:["Clark kent","conner kent","clark junior","Thomas wayne"],answer:"conner kent",id:151},{question:"Who is also known as Hell Blazer",options:["Lucifer","John Constantine","Zatanna Zatara","Mazekin"],answer:"John Constantine",id:152},{question:"What is alterego of Swamp Thing",options:["Alex Danvers","Abby Arcane","Alec Holland","kara Danvers"],answer:"Alec Holland",id:153},{question:"What is alterego of Star Girl",options:["Courtney Whitmore","yolanda","violet","Donna Troy"],answer:"Courtney Whitmore",id:154},{question:"What is Elder Brother of Anti-Monitor",options:["Monitor","Perpetua","World Forger","Darkseid"],answer:"World Forger",id:155},{question:"Who is son of Darkseid",options:["scott free","orion","grail","stepphen wolf"],answer:"orion",id:156},{question:"Who is daughter of the Demon and a member of Teen Titans?",options:["Raven","star fire","wonder girl","bumble bee"],answer:"Raven",id:157},{question:"Where is the head quaters of league of Assassins located?",options:["Mount Rushmore","Nanda Parbat","Manhattan","New york"],answer:"Nanda Parbat",id:158},{question:"Who is head of League of Assassins?",options:["Talia Al ghul","Lady Shiva","Damian Wayne","Ra's Al Ghul"],answer:"Ra's Al Ghul",id:159},{question:"What is alter ego of mister miracle",options:["scott free","orion","micheal keaton","Jimmy olsen"],answer:"scott free",id:160}],m=[{question:"What is alterego of earth-9 dark knight ?",options:["Bruce wayne","selina kyle","Bryce wayne","Thomas wayne"],answer:"Bryce wayne",id:181},{question:"Who is the mother of the Monitor?",options:["perpetua","allwidow","grail","Mazekin"],answer:"perpetua",id:182},{question:"Who is speedster batman from dark multiverse's ?",options:["deathracer","Godspeed","grimripper","Reddeath"],answer:"Reddeath",id:183},{question:"What is alterego of Wild Cat?",options:["Courtney Whitmore","Ted Grant","Kent Nelson","Donna Troy"],answer:"Ted Grant",id:184},{question:"Who is daughter of Darkseid?",options:["Reddaughter","BigBarda","Grail","Allwiow"],answer:"Grail",id:185},{question:"What is the emotion that powers blue lantern rings?",options:["Will","Compassion","Hope","Greed"],answer:"Hope",id:186},{question:"Who is the First Human Green Lantern?",options:["Hall Jordan","John Stewart","Kyle Reyner","Alan Scott"],answer:"Alan Scott",id:187},{question:"What is alterego of DC's Punchline(Anti-Harley Quinn)?",options:["Alex","Alexis","Alec","Red Tool"],answer:"Alexis",id:188},{question:"Who is brother of Martian Manhunter?",options:["Malaque'k","Johnaqa'k","Malafa'k","megafa'k"],answer:"Malafa'k",id:189},{question:"Who is the only JL member escaped from Darkseid's omega beam?",options:["Batman","Superman","Wonder Woman","Flash"],answer:"Batman",id:190}];var p=[{question:"What is alterego of Nine Tails Fox",options:["Red Demon Fox","Kurama","Shukaku","Matatabi"],answer:"Kurama",id:321},{question:"In Fairy Tail, Natsu is a?",options:["Fire Wizard","Demon Slayer","Fire Dragon Slayer","Celeistial Wizard"],answer:"Fire Dragon Slayer",id:322},{question:"What is name of Eren's Titan Form",options:["Attack Titan","Founder Titan","Female Titan","Beast Titan"],answer:"Attack Titan",id:323},{question:"What is the original name of KIRA",options:["LLawliet","Light Yagami","Teru Mikami","Ryuk"],answer:"Light Yagami",id:324},{question:"Who is father of Goten",options:["Piccolo","Bruce Wayne","Vegeta","Goku"],answer:"Goku",id:325}],f=[{question:"In Naruto, how many ninja from Konoha went on to the third stage(after the preliminairies) of the Chunin Exams?",options:["Six","Five","Seven","Four"],answer:"Five",id:351},{question:"In Fairy Tail, who is the first guild master of Fairy Tail?",options:["Gildarts","Makarov Dreyar","Jose Porla","Mavis Vermillion"],answer:"Mavis Vermillion",id:352},{question:"In Demon Slayer, what is the name of Flame Hashira ",options:["Sakonji Urokodaki","Giyu Tomioka","Kyojuro Rengoku","Shinobu Kocho"],answer:"Kyojuro Rengoku",id:353},{question:"In Pokemon, which Pokemon is attached to Slowbro?",options:["Skarmory","Cloyster","Mantine","Shellder"],answer:"Shellder",id:354},{question:"In My Hero Academia, what is the name of Sir Nighteye's protege (Hint: Quirk-Permeation)",options:["Mirio Togata","Mei Hatsume","Tamaki Amajiki","Nejire Hado"],answer:"Mirio Togata",id:355}],w=[{question:"In Naruto, what is the forbidden technique used by Rock Lee that he used on Dosu and Gaara?",options:["Lotus of Destruction","Shadow Lotus","Primary Lotus","Fiery Lotus"],answer:"Primary Lotus",id:381},{question:"In Fairy Tail, what did Natsu say upon seeing Lisanna in Edolas?",options:["'It can't be you.'","'Hi, honey. I'm home.'","'How? You're dead!'","'I found you.'"],answer:"'I found you.'",id:382},{question:"In Attack on Titan, Eren\u2019s nickname in the 104th Training Squad is what?",options:[" Captain Suicide","Rage Machine","Captain Rage","Suicidal Bastard"],answer:"Suicidal Bastard",id:383},{question:"In Death Note, what happens if you accidentally misspel victim's name four times? ",options:["You Die","Nothing","They become immune to Death Note","The Death Note losses its power"],answer:"They become immune to Death Note",id:384},{question:"In My Hero Academia, what is the name of Sir Nighteye's protege (Hint: Quirk-Permeation)",options:["Mirio Togata","Mei Hatsume","Tamaki Amajiki","Nejire Hado"],answer:"Mirio Togata",id:385}];var k=[{question:"What is alterego of ironman",options:["Tony Stark","Steve Rodgers","Robert Downey jr","Pepper potts"],answer:"Tony Stark",id:221},{question:"What is alterego of Black Panther",options:["T'chaka","T'chala","Shuri","Felicia"],answer:"T'chala",id:222},{question:"What is element used in Captain America's Shield",options:["Adamantium","Vibranium","element X","Kryptonite"],answer:"Vibranium",id:223},{question:"What is alterego of Spiderman",options:["Tony Stark","Steve Rodgers","Robert Downey jr","Peter Parker"],answer:"Peter Parker",id:224},{question:"What is alterego of Venom",options:["Tony Stark","Tom Hardy","Eddie Brock","Peter Parker"],answer:"Eddie Brock",id:225},{question:"Who is father of Thor",options:["Odin","Loki","Destroyer","Heimdall"],answer:"Odin",id:226},{question:"What is name of Thor's Hammer",options:["Mjolnir","Myolnir","Miolnir","Mia mia"],answer:"Mjolnir",id:227},{question:"What is alterego of Hawkeye",options:["Clint Barton","Tom Hardy","Sam Wilson","Wilson fisk"],answer:"Clint Barton",id:228},{question:"What is alterego of Hulk",options:["Bruce wayne","Carol danvers","Bruce Banner","Hulk Buster"],answer:"Bruce Banner",id:229},{question:"Which radiation caused te creation of Hulk",options:["cosmic","Gamma","InfraRed","Alpha"],answer:"Gamma",id:230}],y=[{question:"What is alterego of Scarlet Witch",options:["Wanda Maximoff","vanda maximaff","wanda maxximoff","Wanda maximaff"],answer:"Wanda Maximoff",id:251},{question:"What is Father of Iron Man?",options:["Howard Duck","Howard Stark","Henry Stark","Morgan Stark"],answer:"Howard Stark",id:252},{question:"What is alterego of Human Torch",options:["Johnny Storm","Albert Storm","Harry Storm","Sue Storm"],answer:"Johnny Storm",id:253},{question:"What is alterego of Mr.Fantastic?",options:["Reed Richards","Reed Hollands","Johnny richards","Rory Stark"],answer:"Reed Richards",id:254},{question:"What is Color of Time Stone",options:["Orange","Red","Emerald","Yellow"],answer:"Emerald",id:255},{question:"Who is son of Thanos",options:["Thane","Tanatos","deathracer","Deadpool"],answer:"Thane",id:256},{question:"What is alter ego of the Lizard",options:["Dr.summers","Dr.connors","Dr.richards","Dr.smith"],answer:"Dr.connors",id:257},{question:"Where is the head quaters of Avengers located?",options:["Mount Rushmore","Nanda Parbat","Manhattan","New york"],answer:"New york",id:258},{question:"How many Legendary rings that mandarin possess?",options:["Six","Eight","Ten","Seven"],answer:"Ten",id:259},{question:"What is name of first AI in iron man's suit?",options:["Friday","orion","Jarvis","Aida"],answer:"Jarvis",id:260}],g=[{question:"What is alterego of Hob Globin ?",options:["Roderick Kingsley","Norman Osborn","Harry osborn","Flash Thompson"],answer:"Roderick Kingsley",id:281},{question:"Who is the Gaurdian of Web of Destiny?",options:["Madame Xunadu","Madame web","Ancient one","Heimdall"],answer:"Madame web",id:282},{question:"Who is the Unstoppable mutant ?",options:["Wolverine","Quicksilver","Jaggernaut","Deadpool"],answer:"Jaggernaut",id:283},{question:"What is alterego of Black Cat?",options:["Felicia Hardy","Mary jane","Gwen Stacy","Selina kyle"],answer:"Felicia Hardy",id:284},{question:"Who is archnemesis of Hulk?",options:["Red Hulk","Armageddon","red she-hulk","Allwiow"],answer:"Armageddon",id:285},{question:"What is the alterego of Mr.Sinister?",options:["Remy Etienne LeBeau","Remy Emienne LeBeau","sam Etienne LeBeau","Ramy LeBeau"],answer:"Remy Etienne LeBeau",id:286},{question:"Who cursed Deadpool with immortality?",options:["Thanos","Wolverine","Death","weapon x"],answer:"Thanos",id:287},{question:"What is alterego of DareDevil?",options:["Matt Murdack","Matt Murdock","Luke cage","Matthew Richards"],answer:"Matt Murdock",id:288},{question:"What is alterego of doctor strange?",options:["Stephen Strange","Rick Strange","Steaven Strange","Richard Strange"],answer:"Stephen Strange",id:289},{question:"Who is Arch-nemesis of Daredevil?",options:["Wilson Fisk","Punisher","Luke cage","The Beyonder"],answer:"Wilson Fisk",id:290}];var q=[{question:"What is Family name of Levi",options:["Ackerman","Akermaan","Ackarmon","Ackerman"],answer:"Ackerman",id:421},{question:"Along with Eren, who was shot and tranquilized in the back of a wagon?",options:["Mikasa","Historia","Shasha","Armin"],answer:"Historia",id:422},{question:"Who was the only Reiss family member to visit Historia on the farm?",options:["Uri","Drick","Florian","Frieda"],answer:"Frieda",id:423},{question:"Who is the shortest soilder of 104th cadet",options:["Eren","Mikasa","Armin","Historia"],answer:"Historia",id:424},{question:"What is name of the civil war within the empire?",options:["War of Giants","Great Titan War","Black eldien","Great Eldien War"],answer:"Great Titan War",id:425},{question:"Who is responsible for maintaining order within the internment zones such as Liberio?",options:["Survey corps","Marley police","Marley public security","kingsgaurd"],answer:"Marley public security",id:426},{question:"Eren gained Hardening after consuming a bottle labelled?",options:["Hardening","Confidential","Deflection","Armor"],answer:"Armor",id:427},{question:"What is Eren's Titan Form called?",options:["Attack Titan","Armored Titan","Jaw Titan","Colossal Titan"],answer:"Attack Titan",id:428},{question:"Who is the slowest Titan",options:["Attack Titan","Armored Titan","Jaw Titan","Colossal Titan"],answer:"Colossal Titan",id:429},{question:"Which Titan has the hardest skin?",options:["Attack Titan","Armored Titan","Jaw Titan","Colossal Titan"],answer:"Armored Titan",id:430}],W=[{question:"Armin confiscated what from Marlo and Hitch?",options:["Food","Supplies","Rifles","Info"],answer:"Rifles",id:451},{question:"What is Symbol of Eldiens",options:["White band","Tattoos","Shorts","Gears"],answer:"White band",id:452},{question:"Who saved Hange from Cart titan",options:["Jean","Eren","Mikasa","Armin"],answer:"Jean",id:453},{question:"Who saved Mikasa from the Titans",options:["Attack Titan","Female titan","Armored Titan","Armin"],answer:"Attack Titan",id:454},{question:"Who is commander of survey corps?",options:["Erwin","levi","Armin","Mikasa"],answer:"Erwin",id:455},{question:"Who almost killed the beast titan?",options:["Mikasa","Levi","Erwin","Armin"],answer:"Levi",id:456},{question:"Who became the new colossal titan?",options:["Mikasa","Levi","Erwin","Armin"],answer:"Armin",id:457},{question:"Who became the new jaw titan?",options:["Mikasa","Levi","Ymir","Armin"],answer:"Ymir",id:458},{question:"Who is Scientist researching on Titans?",options:["Hange","Ymir","Erwin","Armin"],answer:"Hange",id:459},{question:"Who stopped Annie escape from the fight with Eren?",options:["Mikasa","Levi","Erwin","Armin"],answer:"Mikasa",id:460}],T=[{question:"What is the name of island in Attack on Titan?",options:["Ellis island","Paradis island","Funen island","Elldian island"],answer:"Paradis island",id:481},{question:"Who of the 104th Cadet Corps has been referred to as \u201cGoddess\u201d?",options:["Mikasa","Levi","Historia","Armin"],answer:"Historia",id:482},{question:"Which character has their ears turn red when they lie?",options:["Mikasa","Eren","Historia","Armin"],answer:"Eren",id:483},{question:"How many Titan Shifters are there in AOT?",options:["Six","Ten","Nine","Eleven"],answer:"Nine",id:484},{question:"Which Titan Shifter can maintain their titan form only for short period ?",options:["Attack","Armored","Colossal","Jaw"],answer:"Colossal",id:485},{question:"Who saved armin from Titan's mouth?",options:["Mikasa","Eren","Historia","Levi"],answer:"Eren",id:486},{question:"What is Annie\u2019s last name?",options:["Reiss","Lonarld","Leonhart","Tierce"],answer:"Leonhart",id:487},{question:"What is life span of Titan shifters",options:["9 years","15 years","13 years","12 years"],answer:"13 years",id:488},{question:"Who did Ymir eat to return to her human form?",options:["Attack","Armored","Colossal","Jaw"],answer:"Jaw",id:489},{question:"Which gear is used in fight of retake maria",options:["Anti personnal uni-directional","3d manuer gear","Breach Cannons","Anti personnal omni-directional"],answer:"Anti personnal omni-directional",id:490}];var v=[{question:"What is alterego of Nine Tails Fox",options:["Red Demon Fox","Kurama","Shukaku","Matatabi"],answer:"Kurama",id:521},{question:"Whom did Naruto kiss first?",options:["Sasuke Uchiha","Hinata Hyuga","Fuka","Sakura Haruno"],answer:"Sasuke Uchiha",id:522},{question:"With whose fight did Naruto first use Nine tails Chakra?",options:["Sasuke","Neji","Haku","Gaara"],answer:"Haku",id:523},{question:"Who tricked Naruto into stealing a sacred scroll?",options:["Iruka","Mizuki","Sasuke","Zabuza"],answer:"Mizuki",id:524},{question:"What is another word for ninja?",options:["Genjutsu","Shinobi","Arigato","Chakra"],answer:"Shinobi",id:525},{question:"Which of the legendary sannin becomes the fifth Hokage?",options:["Jiraya","Tsunade","Orochimaru","Kakashi"],answer:"Tsunade",id:526},{question:"Who was the first ninja Sasuke Uchiha copied with the Sharingan?",options:["Rock Lee","Itachi Uchiha","Orochimaru","Naruto"],answer:"Rock Lee",id:527},{question:"Which famous clan was completely massacred?",options:["Uchiha","Hyuuga","Uzamaki","Nara"],answer:"Uchiha",id:528},{question:"What piece of jewelry do the Akatsuki wear?",options:["Earrings","Nose rings","Rings","Anklets"],answer:"Rings",id:529},{question:"What is the village where Naruto lives called?",options:["Sunagakure","Kyuubigakure","Uzamagakure","Konohagakure"],answer:"Konohagakure",id:530}],S=[{question:"How many ninja from Konoha went on to the third stage(after the preliminairies) of the Chunin Exams?",options:["Six","Five","Seven","Four"],answer:"Five",id:551},{question:"What's the name of the leader of the toads?",options:["Wise Frog Master","Giant Toad King","Master Froggo","Great Toad Sage"],answer:"Great Toad Sage",id:552},{question:"How did Hidan (one of the Akatsuki member) die?",options:["He can't die","He was starved","He was trapped in Shadow Posession Jutsu while Ino and Choji killed him","His own god betrayed him"],answer:"He can't die",id:553},{question:"Who gave their life to save Gaara?",options:["Kankuro","Sasori","Chiyo","Fugi"],answer:"Chiyo",id:554},{question:"Who created the Akatsuki?",options:["Orochimar","Tobi","Itachi","Yahiko"],answer:"Yahiko",id:555},{question:"What is Minato's nickname?",options:["The Yellow Flash","The Red Flash","Flash Ninja","Flash of the Leaf"],answer:"The Yellow Flash",id:556},{question:"Which member joined team Taka/Hebi first?",options:["Karin","Jugo","Suigetsu","They all joined at the same time"],answer:"Suigetsu",id:557},{question:"What is Kakashi/Obito's Sharingan ability?",options:["Tsukuyomi","Amaterasu","Kotoamatsukami","Kamui"],answer:"Kamui",id:558},{question:"What was Zabuza's nickname?",options:["The demon of the hidden mist","The silent killer","The demonic killer","The monster of the mist"],answer:"The demon of the hidden mist",id:559},{question:"What is Tsunade's addiction?",options:["Men","Gambling","Work","Alcohol"],answer:"Gambling",id:560}],A=[{question:"In Naruto, what is the forbidden technique used by Rock Lee that he used on Dosu and Gaara?",options:["Lotus of Destruction","Shadow Lotus","Primary Lotus","Fiery Lotus"],answer:"Primary Lotus",id:581},{question:"What does ANBU mean?",options:["Special Unit Forces and Recruits","Special Assassination and Tactical Squad","Undercover Ninjas: Black Operations","Hidden Agendas of Shinobi and Allied Tactics"],answer:"Special Assassination and Tactical Squad",id:582},{question:"How did Sakumo Hatake (Kakashi's father) die?",options:["He got killed on a mission","He was killed by Madara","He naturally died of old age","He committed suicide"],answer:"He committed suicide",id:583},{question:"Who were the first reincarnates of Indra and Ashura?",options:["Naruto and Sasuke","Madara and Hashirama","Sasuke and Itachi","Kakashi and Guy"],answer:"Madara and Hashirama",id:584},{question:"Who was the youngest Jonin?",options:["Kakashi","Itachi","Neji","Sakura"],answer:"Kakashi",id:585},{question:"What does Gaara's tattoo mean?",options:["Orphan","Monster","Love","Hate"],answer:"Love",id:586},{question:"What is Sasuke's team called?",options:["Tiki","Taka","Toka","Toku"],answer:"Taka",id:587},{question:"Which of these characters has Kurama's chakra?",options:["Menma","Guren","Sora","Haku"],answer:"Sora",id:588},{question:"Which of them is not a Kekkei Genkai?",options:["Particle style","Byakugan","Sharingan","Tenseigan"],answer:"Particle style",id:589},{question:"Who is not part of the Team Kurenai?",options:["Shino","Kiba","Hinata","Neji"],answer:"Neji",id:590}];var b=function(e){Object(h.a)(i,e);var a=Object(l.a)(i);function i(e){var n;return Object(r.a)(this,i),(n=a.call(this,e)).selected=function(e){var a=[];a.push(e.target.value),n.setState({options:a,click:!0}),a[0]===n.state.answer?n.setState({color:"green"}):n.setState({color:"red"}),n.props.selection(a[0])},n.state={question:e.question,options:e.options,answer:e.answer,click:!1},n}return Object(u.a)(i,[{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;return t.a.createElement("div",{className:"p-4 m-2"},t.a.createElement("h2",null,this.state.question),this.state.options.map((function(a,i){return t.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn btn-dark m-2",disabled:e.state.click,style:{backgroundColor:"".concat(e.state.color)},key:i,value:a,onClick:e.selected},a)})))}}]),i}(t.a.Component),M=function(e){Object(h.a)(i,e);var a=Object(l.a)(i);function i(e){var n;return Object(r.a)(this,i),(n=a.call(this,e)).changetopic=function(e){n.props.settopic(e.target.value)},n.changedifficulty=function(e){n.props.setdifficulty(e.target.value)},n.getquizquestions=function(){n.props.startquiz()},n.state={topic:e.topic,difficulty:e.difficulty},n}return Object(u.a)(i,[{key:"render",value:function(){return t.a.createElement("div",{className:"text-center"},t.a.createElement("span",{className:"lg-col-4 sm-col-12 m-4"},t.a.createElement("label",{className:"labels m-2"},"TOPIC:"),t.a.createElement("select",{onChange:this.changetopic},t.a.createElement("option",{value:"DC"},"DC"),t.a.createElement("option",{value:"MARVEL"},"MARVEL"),t.a.createElement("option",{value:"AOT"},"ATTACK ON TITAN"),t.a.createElement("option",{value:"NARUTO"},"NARUTO"))),t.a.createElement("span",{className:"lg-col-4 sm-col-12 m-4"},t.a.createElement("label",{className:"labels m-2"},"DIFFICULTY : "),t.a.createElement("select",{onChange:this.changedifficulty},t.a.createElement("option",{value:"easy"},"EASY"),t.a.createElement("option",{value:"moderate"},"MODERATE"),t.a.createElement("option",{value:"hard"},"HARD"))),t.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn btn-success lg-col-4 sm-col-12 p-2 m-3",onClick:this.getquizquestions},"Start Quiz"))}}]),i}(t.a.Component),H=function(e){Object(h.a)(i,e);var a=Object(l.a)(i);function i(e){var n;return Object(r.a)(this,i),(n=a.call(this,e)).getsolution=function(e,a){n.state.responses<5&&(e===a&&n.setState({score:n.state.score+10}),n.setState({responses:n.state.responses+1}))},n.state={questions:[],responses:0,topic:"DC",difficult:"easy",score:0},n}return Object(u.a)(i,[{key:"componentDidMount",value:function(){this.refresher()}},{key:"refresher",value:function(){this.setState({questions:[],responses:0,topic:"DC",difficulty:"easy",score:0})}},{key:"changetopic",value:function(e){this.setState({topic:e})}},{key:"changedifficulty",value:function(e){this.setState({difficulty:e})}},{key:"getquizquestions",value:function(){var e=this.state.topic,a=[];"DC"===e&&(a=function(e){for(var a,i,n=[],t=[0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9],o=t.length;o>0;)i=Math.floor(Math.random()*o),a=t[--o],t[o]=t[i],t[i]=a;if("easy"==e)for(var s=0;s<5;s++)n.push(d[t[s]]);else if("moderate"==e)for(var r=0;r<5;r++)n.push(c[t[r]]);else if("hard"==e)for(var u=0;u<5;u++)n.push(m[t[u]]);return n}(this.state.difficulty)),"MARVEL"===e&&(a=function(e){for(var a,i,n=[],t=[0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9],o=t.length;o>0;)i=Math.floor(Math.random()*o),a=t[--o],t[o]=t[i],t[i]=a;if("easy"==e)for(var s=0;s<5;s++)n.push(k[t[s]]);else if("moderate"==e)for(var r=0;r<5;r++)n.push(y[t[r]]);else if("hard"==e)for(var u=0;u<5;u++)n.push(g[t[u]]);return n}(this.state.difficulty)),"ANIME"===e&&(a=function(e){for(var a,i,n=[],t=[0,1,2,3,4],o=t.length;o>0;)i=Math.floor(Math.random()*o),a=t[--o],t[o]=t[i],t[i]=a;if("easy"==e)for(var s=0;s<5;s++)n.push(p[t[s]]),console.log(p[t[s]].question);else if("moderate"==e)for(var r=0;r<5;r++)n.push(f[t[r]]);else if("hard"==e)for(var u=0;u<5;u++)n.push(w[t[u]]);return n}(this.state.difficulty)),"AOT"===e&&(a=function(e){for(var a,i,n=[],t=[0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9],o=t.length;o>0;)i=Math.floor(Math.random()*o),a=t[--o],t[o]=t[i],t[i]=a;if("easy"==e)for(var s=0;s<5;s++)n.push(q[t[s]]);else if("moderate"==e)for(var r=0;r<5;r++)n.push(W[t[r]]);else if("hard"==e)for(var u=0;u<5;u++)n.push(T[t[u]]);return n}(this.state.difficulty)),"NARUTO"===e&&(a=function(e){for(var a,i,n=[],t=[0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9],o=t.length;o>0;)i=Math.floor(Math.random()*o),a=t[--o],t[o]=t[i],t[i]=a;if("easy"==e)for(var s=0;s<5;s++)n.push(v[t[s]]);else if("moderate"==e)for(var r=0;r<5;r++)n.push(S[t[r]]);else if("hard"==e)for(var u=0;u<5;u++)n.push(A[t[u]]);return n}(this.state.difficulty)),this.setState({questions:a,responses:0})}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;return t.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},t.a.createElement("div",null,0===this.state.responses?t.a.createElement(M,{Box:!0,topic:this.state.topic,difficulty:this.state.diffulty,settopic:function(a){return e.changetopic(a)},setdifficulty:function(a){return e.changedifficulty(a)},startquiz:function(){return e.getquizquestions()}}):null),t.a.createElement("div",{className:"Quizarea"},this.state.questions.length>0&&this.state.responses<5&&this.state.questions.map((function(a){var i=a.question,n=a.options,o=a.answer,s=a.id;return t.a.createElement(b,{question:i,options:n,key:s,answer:o,selection:function(a){return e.getsolution(a,o)}})})),5===this.state.responses?t.a.createElement("div",null,t.a.createElement("h2",{className:"p-2"},"Your Score"),t.a.createElement("h1",{className:"p-2"},this.state.score,"/50"),t.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn btn-primary m-2",onClick:function(){return e.refresher()}},"Retake Quiz")):null))}}]),i}(t.a.Component);var E=function(){return t.a.createElement("div",{className:"App"},t.a.createElement(H,null))};Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));s.a.render(t.a.createElement(t.a.StrictMode,null,t.a.createElement(E,null)),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then((function(e){e.unregister()})).catch((function(e){console.error(e.message)}))}],[[8,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.7a8630a6.chunk.js.map